Ajay has
hey Raju what happened yesterday my bike met with an
accident didi
my bike got damaged due to the accident 5000 rupees were spent
and what happened to your hand didi your
hand got fractured due to the accident so did
you not insure your bike is it
insurance of this bike Raju
by taking bike insurance your vehicle is
safe and
you do not have to bear the expenses caused by the accident not only this
after taking bike insurance in case of an accident, in case of bangles, in case of
burns or due to any natural calamity the
insurance company bears the damages and expenses caused to the vehicle the insurance company has so
many benefits of bike
insurance nachu you can also take insurance for yourself so that
if
any accident happens to you while driving then the
insurance company covers that loss which
means you are also safe with the bike that
is great didi but where can you get this bike insurance
go to ranking point near Airtel Payment Bank i.e. Mohan Telecom and get the bike insurance from
there at Mohan Bhaiya's shop
Mohan shop
and Raju how did you come
My bike got damaged due to an accident and my arm got fractured. I need to get the
bike insured Bhaiya. I should have got it done
earlier, Raju. You have delayed it a lot. No
problem, better late than never.
Bhaiya, I suffered a huge loss and then I woke up. Now you have
insured my vehicle. EP.
Tell me your vehicle number and mobile number.
Bike insurance will be done in 2 to 3 minutes.
My bike number is 48 HPV virus
1234 mobile number 99.
Raju, do I need to get myself insured along with bike insurance?
We are Mohan Bhaiya. This is
Bhartiya Akshara's comprehensive insurance
which covers accidents, theft, burning or even
natural calamities. Now you
and your bike are safe.
Breathe a sigh of relief. Raju, make
your journey pleasant and safe with Bhartiya Raksha two wheeler insurance.
Bhaiya, its claim will be
available at your shop only. No, Raju. Airtel
Payment Bank only has the
right to sell this policy. For claim, you have to call Bharti
AXA customer care number 1800 1032 292. The
claim process of Bhartiya Akshara
is very easy.  Bhaiya,
from where can I get the certificate of this insurance?
Raju, you must have received the link of the insurance certificate through SMS on your phone
or from anywhere, get it
printed and keep it with you, that's it,
thank you Mohan Bhaiya, it has become so
easy to get bike insurance, it is a matter of great happiness
that Airtel Payment Bank has started providing
insurance facility at its nearest breaking point.